Guide to the Vassar College Class Records, 1865-2021
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Class of 1917, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - "To You, the Girls of France" booklet, undated; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Twenty-first Reunion booklet, 1938; [4 copies] (Box 1)
- Class 1918, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - 1918 Roll Call booklet, undated; [3 copies] (Box 1)
  - Alumnae Materials class of 1918, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1918 baccalaureate and graduation materials (Box 1)
  - Class of 1918 Baccalaureate service, 1918 Jun 1 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1918 miscellaneous materials, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1918 reunion booklet, 1959; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Class songs, undated; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Class songs collected by Virginia Burtow (VC 1918, undated (Box 1)
  - Correspondence: Maisry MacCracken to class of 1918, undated (Box 1)
  - Letters from Miss Elizabeth Poucher, undated (Box 1)
  - Lucile Morrison materials class of 1918, undated (Box 1)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1)
  - Posters - 53rd Annual Commencement, with photograph, commencement booklet, and "A Toast to Eighteen" by Burgess Johnson, 1918 (Oversize Box 1)
  - "A Report on 1918's Mini-reunion at Alumnae House,", 1980 Oct 1 (Box 1)
- Class of 1919, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - "The 1918-1919 Students' Handbook,", undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1919 - 55th Reunion Scrapbook, 1974 (Volume)
  - Class of 1919 10th reunion program, 1929 Jun 7 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1919 bulletins, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1919 Commencement week booklet, [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1919 handbook of information, [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1919 Mary (Coven) Jones materials, undated (Box 1)
  - Class songs, undated; [3 copies] (Box 1)
  - "Constitution of the Class of 1919,", undated (Box 1)
  - "Nineteen Speaks" book of poems, undated (Box 1)
  - "Sanity Fare" booklet, undated; [2 copies] (Box 1)
- Class of 1920, [0.6 cubic feet (2 boxes)]
  - "1920's 50th Reunion Memorial Service,", 1970 (Box 2)
  - Audio reels, undated; [2 reels] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1920 "Publications in the Alumnae Collection,", undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1920 100th Anniversary material, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1920 clippings from Reunion exhibit, 1964 Jun (Box 1)
  - Class of 1920 Commencement week booklet (Box 1)
  - Class of 1920 Directory, 1979 Dec 1 (Box 2)
  - Class of 1920 Gertrude Pendill materials, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1920 Marjorie McAndrew materials, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1920 Members of class in "Who's Who,", undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1920 Necrology, undated (Box 2)
  - Class of 1920 Reading Reform Foundation, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1920 scroll, undated (Box 1)
  - Commencement week pamphlet and materials, 1920 (Box 1)
  - Issue of The Miscellany News, 1920 Jun 17 (Box 1)
  - "Junior party - Constance Fisher (Gibson)" photographs/notebook, undated (Box 1)
  - "Pilgrim's Progress - A Celebration of 1920's 50th Reunion 1920-1970,", [3 copies] (Box 2)
  - "Pilgrim's Progress" binder, 1921 May; [2 copies] (Box 2)
  - "Sanity Fare" booklet, undated (Box 1)
  - "Sarah and I" by Sylvia Brockway, undated (Box 1)
  - "Some Champus Kittens" poems, undated (Box 1)
  - Student handbook, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1921, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - 56th Annual commencement booklet, 1921 (Box 1)
  - Class book 1921, undated (Box 1)
  - Class bulletin, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1921 graduation article, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1921 Informal Reunion Attendance List, 1978 Mar 22 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1921 Reunion Review, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1921 Senior Parlor Guest Book, 1920 (Box 1)
  - Class songs, undated (Box 1)
  - Commencement program, 1921 (Box 1)
  - Commencement week booklet, 1921 Jun 11; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Correspondence to a Miss Dorothy Plum and related materials, undated (Box 1)
  - N.Y. Times articles and miscellaneous materials, undated (Box 1)
  - Pictures of bells designed by Rebecca Handy Mayes (VC 1921), undated (Box 1)
  - "Some Champus Kittens,", undated (Box 1)
  - Vassar Verse booklet, undated; [2 copies] (Box 1)
- Class of 1922, [1 cubic foot (3 boxes)]
  - 1922 Founder's Day booklet (Box 3)
  - 1922 News Bulletin, undated; [2 copies] (Box 3)
  - 50th reunion bulletin, 1972; [3 copies] (Box 3)
  - 50th Reunion materials, 1972 (Box 3)
  - Alumnae address/information book, undated (Box 2)
  - Baccalaureate service, 1922 Jun 11 (Box 3)
  - Christmas card of E. Bruce (Lee) Kennedy (VC 1922), undated (Box 3)
  - Class bulletin, undated (Box 3)
  - Class minute book of 1922, 1918-1935 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1922 40th reunion, 1962 (Box 3)
  - Class of 1922 Senior Parlor Guest Book (Volume)
  - Class of 1922 reunion materials, undated; [2 folders] (Box 3)
  - Class songs, undated (Box 3)
  - Commencement week booklet, 1922 Jun 10; [3 copies] (Box 2)
  - Commencement week booklet, 1922 Jun 10 (Box 3)
  - Commencement week pamphlet, 1922 Jun (Box 3)
  - Fay Pike (VC 1922) materials, undated (Box 2)
  - "Follies of 1922,", 1920 Nov 13 (Box 2)
  - Helen Taylor (VC 1922) materials, undated (Box 3)
  - Manuscript of Marie (Novakova) Stankevich (VC 1922), June 1969 (Box 2)
  - "Memory and Fellowship Book,", undated (Box 3)
  - "Outlines of English Political and Constitutional History,", undated (Box 2)
  - Photograph - unidentified portrait, circa 1922 (Oversize Box 1)
  - "VC Course of Study in the Freshman Year,", undated (Box 3)
- Class of 1923, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - 2 keys marked "Vassar Locks,", undated (Box 1)
  - Class news bulletin - first annual edition, 1931 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1923 "Cabbages and Kings,", 1923 Dec 8 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1923 clippings, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1923 report of second reunion, 1925 Jun 5 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1923 Senior Parlor Guest Book, circa 1923 (Box 2)
  - Class songs, undated; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Necrology and Newspaper articles on Doris Marks, undated (Box 1)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 1)
- Class 1924, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - 59th Annual commencement pamphlet, 1924 Jun 10 (Box 1)
  - Class sash, undated (Box 1)
  - Class songs, undated (Box 1)
  - Class tote bags, undated; [2 items] (Box 1)
  - Clippings, undated (Box 1)
  - Commencement week booklet, 1924 (Box 1)
  - Evelyn Kuhs Kirby: Diploma: French Fencing, undated (Box 1)
  - Kathleen Jackson (VC 1924) thesis, undated; [9 folders] (Box 1)
  - List of "major class of 1924 publications available in VC Library,", undated (Box 1)
  - Photographs of Laura Morris Burnett (VC 1924), undated (Box 1)
  - Reunion folder class of 1924, 1982 Apr (Box 1)
  - Vassar songs, undated (Box 1)
  - Yellow felt beret, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1925, [0.6 cubic feet (2 boxes)]
  - 45th reunion materials, 1970 (Box 2)
  - 50th reunion songs, 1975 (Box 2)
  - Alumnae questionnaire results, undated (Box 2)
  - Class bulletin, undated (Box 2)
  - Class of 1925 card case, locker 432, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1925 photographs - from Hope Frenan?, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1925 Treasurer's notebook, undated (Box 2)
  - Class songs, undated; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Commencement and reunion materials, 1925; [2 folders] (Box 1)
  - Correspondence to Miss V. Louise Kellogg, undated (Box 2)
  - "Salve - A Tribute from the Faculty to the Alumnae,", undated (Box 2)
  - Treasurer documents, undated (Box 2)
  - Vassar alumnae address book, undated; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - VC miscellaneous photographs, undated (Box 2)
  - "Vital Statistics of the Class of 1925,", undated (Box 2)
- Class of 1926, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - "Good Roommating - A Magazine for Every Freshman,", undated (Box 1)
  - "Rough Housekeeping" magazine, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1926 bulletin, undated; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Commencement week booklet, 1926 (Box 1)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1927, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - "Baby's Book,", undated (Box 1)
  - Book: "Apostle of Democracy, The Life of Lucy Maynard Salmon" by Louise Fargo Brown, undated (Box 1)
  - Borg-Sundman, Margit - 60th reunion greetings, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Class day exercises, 1927; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Class ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1927 60th reunion directory, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1927 commencement photographs - daisy chain bearers (Box 1)
  - Class of 1927 commencement programs (Box 1)
  - Class of 1927 directory, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1927 directory, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1927 misc. programs, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1927 photographs of Hall Plays, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1927 Sixty-second commencement (Box 1)
  - Class songs, undated; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Commencement week booklet, 1927 (Box 1)
  - First hall reunion bulletin, 1927 Dec 2; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Junior promenade booklet, undated (Box 1)
  - "My Memory Book,", undated (Box 1)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1)
  - "The Red Dragon Nursery Book,", undated (Box 1)
  - Reunion Bulletin no. 2, 1929 Jun 7; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Reunion Bulletin no. 3, 1931 Jun 5; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Student handbook, undated (Box 1)
  - Students' Association booklet, undated (Box 1)
  - "Tristan and Renart: Two Tricksters'" by Nancy Freeman Regalado, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1928, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - 1928 necrology, undated (Box 1)
  - Alumnae correspondence/reports, undated (Box 1)
  - Audiocassette - VC Centennial, 1961 (Box 1)
  - Audiocassette - VC Reunion, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Audiocassette - VC Reunion, 1971 (Box 1)
  - Class day exercises, undated (Box 1)
  - Class ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1928 60th reunion directory, 1988; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1928 address directory, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1928 Bulletin, 1938 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1928 Senior promenade, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1928 Thirty-eight year report, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Class songs, undated; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Clippings, undated (Box 1)
  - "A Colloquim of Archaics" program, undated (Box 1)
  - Commencement week booklet, 1928 (Box 1)
  - Constitution of the class of 1928, undated (Box 1)
  - Correspondence to and checks received from Faith D. Waterman, undated (Box 1)
  - "In Memory of Catherine "Kitty" Stuntz de Coup-Crank,", undated (Box 1)
  - Letter from Eugenia Litchfield (Stubbs) (VC 1928), 1988 May 31 (Box 1)
  - Negatives of commencement from Constance W. Goss, undated (Box 1)
  - Newsletter by Mary Saylor Mulhausen (VC 1928), undated (Box 1)
  - Notice - "Vassar announces winners of Kazan Prize,", undated (Box 1)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1)
  - Pictures of commencement from Constance W. Goss, undated (Box 1)
  - Program/notices for "My Fair Lady" at Michigan Opers Theater, undated (Box 1)
  - Sixty-third commencement, undated (Box 1)
  - Vassarion address book, undated (Box 1)
  - VC play program, undated (Box 1)
  - "When We Were as Young as You" by class of 1928, undated; [4 copies] (Box 1)
- Class of 1929, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Class of 1929 French Manuscript, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1929 newspaper articles, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1929 Reunion and Alumnae materials, undated; [3 folders] (Box 1)
  - Class reunion + commencement materials, undated (Box 1)
  - The Miscellany News - Special Issue, 1971 Jun 4 (Oversize Box 1)
  - Music manuscript, undated (Box 1)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1)
  - Sheet music (handwritten) - "Rôle de Robin,", circa 1929 (Oversize Box 1)
  - "To The Freshman -or- As They Prefer to Call Themselves, 1929,", undated; [2 copies] (Box 1)
- Class of 1930, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - 1930 calendar, undated (Box 1)
  - Class day exercises, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1930 directory, 1990; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1930 felt letters, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1930 reunion, 1976 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1930 reunion, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1930 reunion materials, undated (Box 1)
  - Commencement week booklet, 1930 Jun 10; [3 copies] (Box 1)
  - Memorial Service 50th reunion, 1980 Jun 7 (Box 1)
  - Sixty-fifth commencement booklet, 1930; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Sixty-sixth commencement booklet, 1930 (Box 1)
  - Watercolor on a 1988 calendar by Droulihet, Elizabeth P. Moffat, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1931, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Alumnae materials: letters, updates, notices, undated (Box 1)
  - Biographical questionnaires from 25th reunion, 1956; [4 folders] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1931 alumnae information, undated; [3 folders] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1931 Scrapbook, 1965-1967 (Volume)
  - Commencement week booklet, 1931 Jun 6 (Box 1)
  - Letters and postcards, undated (Box 1)
  - Newspaper articles: Yale-Vassar merger, Mary Bunting materials, misc materials, undated (Box 1)
  - Wallace M. Yater material, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1932, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - "'32 Exhibit questionnaire - Part II,", undated (Box 1)
  - 1932 donation records, undated (Box 1)
  - 50th reunion photographs, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Class correspondence from Dottie C. Roudebush, undated (Box 1)
  - Class ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - Class materials collected by Mary Wallace McLeod (VC 1932), undated; [4 folders] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1932 44th reunion supplement, 1976 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1932 50th reunion report, 1982; [4 copies] (Box 1)
  - Class reunion materials, undated (Box 1)
  - Collection of materials on the theatrical history of St. Louis, g. Dorothy Jean Coleman (VC 1932), undated (Box 1)
  - Commencement week booklet, 1932 Jun 10 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence from Sally Bartlett (VC 1932), undated (Box 1)
  - Grades of Elizabeth Fish (VC 1932), undated (Box 1)
  - Jane Ketchum's AAVC Files, 1953-1981 (Box 1)
  - Lyrics to "Jacob's Ladder,", undated (Box 1)
  - Memorial service - 65th reunion, 1997 Jun 7 (Box 1)
  - Miscellany News 1932 graduation issue (Box 1)
  - "My Memory Book,", undated (Box 1)
  - Student handbook, undated (Box 1)
  - VC Chapel Reunion Sunday service, 1976 May 23 (Box 1)
  - VC Christmas music sung by the choir, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1933, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - "Alice Again" program, 1933 Jun 10 (Box 1)
  - Cartoons presented to returning members of the class of 1933 at their 50th reunion, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1933 45th reunion bulletin, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1933 55th reunion bulletin, 1988; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Commencement week booklet, 1933 Jun 9 (Box 1)
  - Newspaper article "Life at Vassar College,", undated (Box 1)
  - Sixty-eighth commencement booklet, 1933 Jun 12; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - "Vassar" drawn by Anne Cleveland and Jean Anderson, undated (Box 1)
  - Vassarion Address book, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1934, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - 1934 class questionnaire, undated (Box 1)
  - 65th reunion memorial service, 1997 Jun 7 (Box 1)
  - Class ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - Materials relating to the class of 1934, donated by Lucy Schneider, undated (Box 1)
  - Memoir - "The Life of Mary G. Clarke" (mother of Shirley Clarke Van Cleef, VC 1934), undated (Box 1)
  - Miscellany News publication, undated (Box 1)
  - Pocket calendar, undated (Box 1)
  - Program for "College Bored,", undated (Box 1)
  - Program for "Phoebe in Fumbleland,", undated (Box 1)
  - Sixty-ninth commencement program, 1934 (Box 1)
  - "Vague" magazine, 1931 May (Box 1)
- Class of 1935, [0.6 cubic feet (2 boxes)]
  - "Biographical Bulletin,", 1935-1951 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1935 50th reunion directory, 1985; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1935 65th reunion directory, 2000; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1935 alumnae donation record book, undated; [2 books] (Box 2)
  - Class of 1935 class study, undated; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1935 general correspondence - Folder 1, 1973-1977 (Box 2)
  - Class of 1935 general correspondence - Folder 2, 1981-1993 (Box 2)
  - Class of 1935 general correspondence - Folder 3, 1997-2005 (Box 2)
  - Class of 1935 memorial fund, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1935 tote bag, undated (Box 1)
  - Commencement events program, 1935 (Box 1)
  - Commencement notices, 1935 (Box 1)
  - Commencement week booklet, 1935 Jun 7 (Box 1)
  - Conference - "Some Correlations in Romantic Art, Literature, and Music,", undated (Box 1)
  - Library gift records, undated (Box 2)
  - Notice for purchasing tickets to VC Reunion, undated (Box 1)
  - Program for "Passe News of Vassar College,", undated; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Seventieth commencement program, 1935 Jun 10 (Box 1)
  - "Student Government at Vassar,", 1934-1935 (Box 1)
- Class of 1936, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Class of 1936 45th reunion records, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1936 50th reunion records, 1986 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1936 55th reunion, 1991 Jun (Box 1)
  - Correspondence to Lola Boyd in preparation for 50th reunion, 1986 Jun (Box 1)
  - Louise Dudley Breckenridge Fund records, undated (Box 1)
  - Preparation for 50th reunion, 1986 Jun (Box 1)
  - Seventy-First commencement program, 1936 Jun 8 (Box 1)
- Class of 1937, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - 1936 combination calendar, undated (Box 1)
  - 50th reunion record, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Class ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - Commencement week booklet, 1937 Jun 4; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - "Information for New Students" pamphlet, undated (Box 1)
  - Program for "'37 Varieties,", undated (Box 1)
  - Program for "Recital by Marta Milinowski,", undated (Box 1)
  - Program for "The World We Live In,", undated (Box 1)
  - Radio City Music Hall program, undated (Box 1)
  - Seventy-seventh commencement program, 1937 Jun 7; [3 copies] (Box 1)
  - Student handbook, undated (Box 1)
  - Vassar campus map, undated (Box 1)
  - "Vassar College and its Eight Presidents" exhibition, 1986 Oct 11 (Box 1)
- Class of 1938, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Class of 1938 25th reunion book, 1963 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1938 30th reunion questionnaire, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1938 reunion gift countdown, 1982 Jun 4 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1938 sixteen-year report, 1954 (Box 1)
  - Gertrude King's annotated reunion booklets, undated (Box 1)
  - Planned attendance list for 1938 reunion, undated (Box 1)
  - Seventy-third commencement program, 1938; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Seventy-third commencement Sunday Evening Music program, 1938 (Box 1)
  - Songs for Class of 1938 reunion, undated (Box 1)
  - Speech to the Class of 1938 by Eleanor Ruggles, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1939, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Book - "Vassar College Art Library,", undated (Box 1)
  - Cartoon of Class of 1939, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1939 (?) - Group photograph, formal event, 1935 Feb 16 (Oversize Box 1)
  - Envelopes from Alumnae House, undated; [11 envelopes] (Box 1)
  - Photographs sent in by Mary M. Peabody, undated; [6 envelopes] (Box 1)
  - Poems by Christine Ramsey Lyman (VC 1939), undated (Box 1)
  - Stationary from Alumnae House, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1940, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Biographical questionnaires, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1940 25th reunion bulletin, 1965 Jun 11 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1940 alumnae records/addresses, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1940 directory, 1978 Jun (Box 1)
  - Invitations to commencement week, undated; [2 envelopes] (Box 1)
- Class of 1941, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Christmas card from Class of 1941, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1941 directory, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Studies and Sports at VC - reprinted from 1941 Vassarion, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1942, [1.3 cubic feet (2 boxes)]
  - Article - "'42 at Fifty,", 1992; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1942 directory, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1942 surveys, undated (Box 2)
  - Class secretary record book, undated (Box 1)
  - Documents from the estate of Eleanor Stoddard, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1943, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - 78th commencement booklet, 1943 (Box 1)
  - Article - "Women Pilots Fly Into Town,", undated (Box 1)
  - "Class Day Play - Life scene" by Mary Bartlett Gibney and Peggy Masback, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1943 alumni information - grad year, relatives, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1943, "50th Reunion Wrap-up - The Way We Were, 1993 Jun 3; [2 copies] (Box 1)
- Class of 1944, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - AAVC 100th anniversary donation notice, undated (Box 1)
  - "About the Bookshop" booklet, undated (Box 1)
  - Booklet - "Henry Noble MacCracken,", undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1944 40th reunion materials, 1984 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1944 50th reunion questionnaire, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1944 alumni information - grad year, relatives, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1944 commencement exercises, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1944 misc reunion materials, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1944 reunion bulletin, 1980 Jun (Box 1)
  - Class of 1944 songs + info on songs, undated (Box 1)
  - "The Gall" newspaper vol. XIV, 1959 Feb 21 (Box 1)
  - "Information for new students" pamphlet, undated (Box 1)
  - Information on class donations, undated (Box 1)
  - Letter from Alice Dun about Peace Corp trip to Malawi, undated (Box 1)
  - Letter from [Elizabeth?] Ferry Coonley to Julia Cuniberti (VC 1944), 1954 Oct 5 (Box 1)
  - List of class memorabilia, undated (Box 1)
  - Notice from VC President concerning Cambodia protests, undated (Box 1)
  - Notice on racial equality sit-in at VC from president, undated (Box 1)
  - "Old Aunt Lola's Tall Tale" by Lydia O'Neal, undated (Box 1)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1)
  - "Physical Education at Vassar College" booklet, undated (Box 1)
  - Program for "Alice in Wonderland,", undated (Box 1)
  - Program for "Candidata,", undated (Box 1)
  - Program for "The Tempest,", undated (Box 1)
  - Program for a performance by Hunter + Vassar dance groups, undated (Box 1)
  - Program for a performance by Vassar + Yale glee clubs, undated (Box 1)
  - Reunion notices, undated (Box 1)
  - Sheet music - " 1944 Hymnal,", undated; [3 copies] (Box 1)
  - "So You're Coming to Vassar" from the Student's Association, undated (Box 1)
  - "Some Aspects of 1944,", undated; [3 copies] (Box 1)
  - Speech at convocation by MacCracken - "Vandals and Vandal-Worship,", undated (Box 1)
  - Student handbook, undated (Box 1)
  - "Vassar Alumnae Newsletter,", undated (Box 1)
  - Vassar Library handbook and map, undated (Box 1)
  - VC seal belt buckle, undated (Box 1)
  - "What Every Woman Knows" by Diantha Somerville, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1945-4
  - No materials
- Class of 1945, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - "1974 Ivan Environman Calendar of Virgin Islands Cultural & Natural History, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1945 alumni information - grad year, relatives, undated (Box 1)
  - Commencement exercises booklet, 1945 (Box 1)
  - Painted paper acorn, undated (Box 1)
  - "Vassar 1945 in 1970: 25th Reunion Profile of a Class,", [3 copies] (Box 1)
- Class of 1946, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Class of 1946 reunion materials, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1946 alumni information - graduation year, relatives, undated (Box 1)
  - "Vassar - A View From the Tower 1943-'46" compiled by Kitty Jenkins Sutherland, undated; [3 copies] (Box 1)
- Class of 1947, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - "50th Reunion Class of 1947: in memory,", 1997 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1947 50th reunion singalong, 1997; [3 copies] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1947 questionnaires for class book (blank), undated (Box 1)
  - "A Letter to the Recipient of the Polly Richardson Lukens Memorial Scholarship,", undated; [3 copies] (Box 1)
  - Notice on Polly Richardson Lukens scholarship, undated (Box 1)
  - "The Perils of Persis Poltergeist" program, undated (Box 1)
  - Photograph - children of Marjorie (Wykes) Hartger, undated (Box 1)
  - "To the Class of 1947 from the Vassar Community Church" booklet, undated (Box 1)
  - "A Vassar Girl is a Vassar Girl, Even at a Chateau" article, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1948, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Letter to 1948 from Elaine Cruikshank Luckey, undated (Box 1)
  - Photograph - children of Joan (Allen) Kastner (VC 1948), undated (Box 1)
  - "Potomac Almanac - THINK Edition,", 1965 Jun 18 (Box 1)
  - "Potomac Almanac,", 1961 Jul 28 (Box 1)
  - "The Vassar Calendar" 1948, undated (Box 1)